May I help you, sir?
Ah yes, I have a headache,
and I'm allergic to aspirin.
- Do you have something?
- Excuse me?
I have a headache,
and I'm allergic to aspirin.
Do you have something?
No, no!
When you don't understand
the customer,
you must apologize correctly
and convey that.
I'm sorry.
But, if you can't understand
even this much,
what are you going to do?
Weren't you an English teacher?
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just passing by.
What about you,
what happened?
I'm no longer the director,
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
I am no longer a teacher, either.
I was reminiscing
about when Seirin Academy
first started.
Every morning I'd go
around like this
and look at all the school
buildings.
Have you found Onizuka-
sensei yet?
No...
I wonder what he's doing
in the shape he's in?
I'm sure he's thinking
of something.
I wonder.
What are you saying?
If you don't believe in him,
then what?
What are we going to do?
Just when the troublemaker
is gone and peace
has returned to our academy,
this happens!
The parents have sent us letters.
Their children are refusing
to go to school.
They're asking what
the meaning of this is?
Would you be quiet,
Hakamada-sensei!
- Then what should we do?
- Excuse me, Head Teacher!
Tôdô-san is here.
I don't know a thing about this!
Uchiyamada-sensei,
it seems that there isn't a single
student at school.
Yes, well...
But please don't worry.
We will talk to the students
and bring them right back
to school.
There's no need for that.
This is the new director
I have recommended,
the director from Jinnan
Academy, Kamimura-san.
Pleased to meet you.
Excuse me, what do you mean?
Seirin Academy will fall under
the jurisdiction of Jinnan Academy.
- But!
- Do not worry.
All the student will have a week,
until September 22nd,
to transfer to Jinnan Academy.
We will inform their parents.
Then, what about us?
I will write letters of introduction
for everyone.
Please look for a new place
of employment.
But wait! Does that mean
we're fired?
At our Jinnan Academy,
we have many talented teachers.
I think it would be too
difficult for you to keep up
- with that kind of level.
- Then what about the campus?
In one week, it will be torn down
and made into athletic grounds.
But wait! This is not what we
talked about!
- If you'll excuse us.
- Wait!
Tôdô-san! Tôdô-san!
Where have you gone,
Onizuka-sensei?
- Hey Missus, gyôza today.
- Coming right up!
Man, but why is that hospital
food so crappy!
- You're here! Onitchi!
- What's up with you guys?
We're boycotting class
until you come back.
It's not just us,
all the students are.
- You shouldn't waste your time.
- What do you mean?
Well, no matter how
much you tried,
I would have been fired anyway.
You don't want to return
to school?
Are you just going to forget
about us?
Sorry, but I'm busy.
Get the bill.
- Hey! The tab!
- Hey, Noboru, you get it.
Murai's mom helped me out.
So, for now...
I'm Great Driver Onizuka!
With this, both the classes
and athletics,
this year is over.
How can you say that?!
- I'm sorry.
- What about our salary.
We are getting it, right?
- I think so.
- You think so?!
It's because you were so lax
that this happened!
That's how I felt, too,
on how you were handling
the academy's future.
Well, the one person who
is betraying us
and going to Jinnan Academy
has no right to talk that way!
What?!
Um, that and this are totally
different things!
How lucky, these people who
have connections
with the Ministry of Education.
Don't be so bitter just
because you
- haven't found anything yet.
- What do you mean by that!
I've always been meaning
to tell you
about that superior attitude
of yours!
Yes well, I've hated that hot
headedness of yours!
Excuse me! So what are we
going to do?
Shut up!
Always asking
"What should we do?"!
You're the school supervisor,
aren't you?
Well, I've been thinking
of a lot of things!
I was originally against
staging the putsch.
What do you mean?
You were so happy that it would
get rid of Onizuka.
It's no use talking
about that now!
As an educator, why don't you
take a stronger attitude!
Quiet!
You know, I hate how you're
always preaching!
Haven't you realized it yet?
That not only the students
but the teachers also dislike you?
How rude! What do you
mean by that?
- It's exactly as he says!
- Why, you old fart!
Tôdô-san, thank you
for everything.
But you're something else,
Kamimura-san.
Oh no, not at all.
Turning Seirin Academy into
a dedicated athletic grounds.
If you take the national title
in baseball or soccer,
Jinnan's reputation
will rise higher.
In other words, you'll be able
to obliterate all rivals.
On top of that, with the transfer
of Seirin students,
Jinnan's university admittance
rate will go up even more.
It's killing two, no... three,
birds with one stone.
In any case, your political
cooperation
has been a great help.
How convenient, that my son
caused such an incident.
What's that, a gift from above?
That's saying a bit much,
don't you think, Kamimura-san?
Well, then.
Shin'ichi,
remember this about people.
This is also a way
of doing things.
Shin'ichi?
What do you want?
Please...
Please ask your dad to return
Onizuka to our school.
We're no good without him.
We told you, we'd do anything
to protect Onizuka.
Like always, it looks like you guys
don't understand a thing.
What's that?
While you guys were
not in school,
the situation's gotten even
more serious.
Step right up! Step right up!
Step right up! Step right on up!
Hey, you there!
How about some takoyaki?
It be great to have
a meal with you...
I heard from the students
that you
were working as a truck driver.
I needed some money,
so I'm working here.
- Would you like some?
- No, thank you!
It's really good.
Don't you know that the school
is in trouble?
- So it seems.
- So it seems?
Then shouldn't you be doing
something about it, not this!
And besides...
Why didn't you call?
I've been looking all
over for you!
Or do you think I'm of no
help to you?
Are you saying you
don't care about me?
- Say something!
- Why didn't you say anything?
That you quit school?
Didn't you say?
"Leave the school up to me."
That's why I didn't worry.
Oh yeah, I heard you
got into stewardessing.
I'm in training.
That's great! Your dream's
come true!
But what are you going to do?
Aren't you going to return
to school anymore?
Don't you care what happens
to Seirin Academy anymore?
It doesn't matter!
Because I'm not a teacher.
Excuse me.
- Welcome.
- May I have two?
Coming right up!
I understand.
If you'll excuse me.
Have a good day.
Here young miss, 350 yen.
This is 400 yen, here,
I'll give you an extra.
- Thank you!
- See ya!
Well then, please start.
What's going on?
Welcome!
Is this it?
Kind of a lonely going away
party, don't you think?
Hey, where's the head teacher?
That's alright, no need for him.
He's probably worried
because others
have already found new jobs.
At this age, having a going
away party hurts.
Don't you think, Fujitomi-sensei?
Yes, well...
Why don't we stop talking
about this, it's depressing.
You can say that because
your position is set.
Hello, I'm reporting
from the scene.
This morning, at eleven o'clock
at Seirin Academy,
that violent teacher who seriously
injured eleven high school
students has caused
another incident.
While being investigated
by the police,
he has holed up in the academy
that he was fired from.
We have not been able
to see anything
of what is going on inside.
We do not know what
the situation is
with the students taken hostage.
Thank you, Terada-san.
We understand your daughter
is among them, Aizawa-sensei.
Yes, we're worried about
the children.
That man must have
threatened them!
All of the parents were overjoyed
to hear that our children
would be admitted
to Jinnan Academy.
What are you going to do?
There's no way I'm going
to quit classes early!
And there's ten years left
on our loan.
It's because you went
and bought that Benz!
I'm never going to trust you ever!
What was that about you'll
become principal any day now?
Do you have any skills?
Can you find a new job?
I'll have you sign this!
Please, don't say that!
As you can see,
it is in the contract.
There is absolutely no
wrongdoing on our part.
In other words, this is trespassing
and illegal occupation.
So how do you intend to deal
with this now.
In any case, the children
are in there.
To us, their safety
is most important.
It seems that he will not
listen to us.
What's that?
EVERYONE COME AND MEET
IN THE SCHOOL!
This is obviously to stir us up.
At this rate, we will need
to turn to the police
to seek their release.
Who's there!
Fuyutsuki-sensei!
It's me.
- Worried about Onizuka?
- Well, yes.
Come with me.
Sorry 'bout this, Saeijima.
If you're going to apologize,
you should apologize to her.
Is everyone doing alright?
Yeah.
What are you planning to do?
You're not thinking of something
dangerous, are you?
There's no need to worry.
Were you planning on doing
this from the start?
You're always like this!
You never tell me anything.
Remember when I was undecided
about taking
the stewardess exam?
You said then...
You said, if I decide for you,
would you do it?
At that time, if I said I would,
what would you have said?
Just how do you think of me?
Can't you at least tell
me that much?
Tell me.
Is this good enough?
Me too...
I want to be with you.
Sorry to interrupt this
great moment.
Hey you,
you shouldn't be in here.
There's nothing to see, go on.
I have succeeded in entering
the building
at the Musashino Seirin
barricade incident.
We are now going to investigate
and gather information.
The barricaded entrance
is coming into view.
However, aside from that,
there doesn't seem
to be anything much
different inside.
This is terrible!
Everyone wake up!
Please, wake up!
Just what is this violent
teacher thinking,
and what is he planning?
Let's take a look.
Oh! It appears they are all being
held in this classroom!
No! Stop it!
This is because you wouldn't
listen to me.
- Please! Don't kill me!
- That Onizuka!
- Please! No!
- One of the students!
This is it! This is the end!
- Let's call the head teacher!
- It's no use!
He's useless!
Just what kind of horrendous
things are going on inside?
Everyone... Everyone,
we would like you
to witness it with your
very own eyes!
What do you think you're doing?
Please! Don't kill me!
You're the one who
betrayed me!
Don't kill me!
You're going to hell!
She's gotten pretty good.
But don't you think I'm better?
Please! Don't kill me!
Oh, come on!
Never mind, then!
How's everyone?
Today, I asked my supervisor
and the staff to film
my practicing.
You know, I'm really glad
I came to Okinawa.
I'm really glad Onizuka-sensei
and all of you supported me.
Even now, I love Musashino
Seirin Academy.
That's why if anyone asks about
my school background,
I'll reply proudly,
I am a product of Musashino
Seirin Academy High.
Tôdô-san, just what is this?
Well said Tomoko!
Bye bye!
We'll now enter the classroom!
Are you getting this?
We're now entering
the classroom,
this is an exclusive scoop!
The problem teacher is here.
You aren't planning on
demanding a ransom, are you?
Um, what were you
doing just now?
Well you see, a student who
was in this class until recently
sent us this video.
I wanted to show this
to everyone.
- What?!
- Is this on?
Yes, that's right.
Well then, hello everyone,
Nomura Tomoko is aiming
to be Japan's top idol.
Please support her!
And by the way,
her foster parent is myself,
Eikichi Onizuka, 26 years old,
occupation: teacher,
blood type: O, sign: Taurus.
Types I like are
Hirosue and Matsu Takako.
And my policy is...
Above all, I am a teacher.
So this isn't a group abduction?
That's quite alright.
Thank you, if you'll excuse us.
Just what is that Onizuka
thinking?
Just as screwed up as ever,
watching a video at a time
like this!
But... she's opened her entire
future now, Nomura-san.
That's right.
In school, no one would have
thought anything of her.
You never know with children.
You never know what kind
of talents they may have.
The one who changed her...
It was Onizuka-sensei.
Because of him,
Nomura-san was able
to discover her own talent.
Don't you think people's
lives are determined
by the people they encounter?
The truth is, everyone teases me
and disregards me,
but the determination for me
to go to school, to do my best...
It was because I've met
Onizuka-sensei.
Not only that,
but even at my age, I've been
able to grab onto a dream!
My dream...
It's the same as Onizuka-sensei's.
Above all, to be a teacher!
There's something I want
everyone to hear.
Why did you all want
to become teachers?
I...
Once, when Nomura-san
asked me that...
That I was forced into it
and happened
to pass by chance,
I couldn't tell her.
I was too embarrassed
to tell her that
I was unwillingly a teacher.
But after I met Onizuka-san,
my feelings started to change.
At first, I thought, what kind
of reckless man is this?
But then, while
I was with Onizuka-sensei,
I began to see the joys
of being a teacher.
I began to think, being a teacher
is a wonderful job!
I began to understand that this
work had infinite potential.
But...
I am no longer a teacher.
Unlike the rest of you,
I am no longer a teacher!
Um...
Well, I...
There's been something
I've been thinking about.
Excuse me...
Take the character oni
from Onizuka,
and when you add on
the character iu,
you get the character
for tamashii - soul.
You see, that soul...
I don't think I've ever put any
soul into my job as a teacher.
Me too.
When I first became a teacher,
back then, I did so with
a pure soul.
Yes, just when did we
become like this?
What are you all doing?
Let's become
"Great Teachers" too!
Yes! Because we've all been
Great Teachers!
We have to graduate from being
self-serving teachers, don't we?
Let's fight along
with Onizuka-sensei!
Nakamaru-sensei!
That's how I felt from before!
Well then, shall we get Seirin
Academy back
to how it should be?
PROTECT THE MUSASHINO
SEIRIN ACADEMY
CAMPUS FESTIVAL TRADITION!
Please help our school!
Excuse me, please sign this.
EXPLOSIVES
There's an age restriction.
Well, could you...
Yes, well, Uchiyamada-san,
if you had some qualifications...
- I do.
- Yes, what is it?
My thirty years in the teaching
staff has developed
- willpower and strength.
- Yes, well...
Willpower and strength is fine,
but what I mean is experience
with computers or software.
Computers?
- Dear!
- Oh!
Don't worry, I've been persistent
and they've finally found
me something.
What's this,
a job at a supermarket?
There's no way you
can do this, Papa!
The customers will all run away
when they see your face, Papa!
Hey, what are you doing!
Papa, this isn't the kind
of work you want to do, is it?
Being a teacher is the only
thing you can do.
You guys...
You should stop playing around
and get a job too.
Hey now! I know you've got
a secret savings, you know.
That's right! Why don't you find
a rich man to marry?
You got dumped by Eikichi-san,
didn't you?
Shut up!
Let's do our best!
Tôdô-san, what should we do?
This will interfere with our plans!
What are you so worried about,
Kamimura-san.
We're the ones who
are legally correct.
So what if they get petitions
and stage a sit-in?
It's too late for them
to do anything now.
Yes, I know...
Come tomorrow, the 23rd,
all of Seirin Academy will
become Jinnan Academy's.
There's nothing to worry about.
The atmosphere is becoming
increasingly bad,
even now it looks like
it might rain?
But look, the teachers
of Musashino Seirin Academy
are still continuing their sit-in
at the south entrance.
As of today, this has become
Jinnan Academy's property.
They have no right to be here.
We cannot tolerate this intrusion.
There is no point in this.
This is our final warning.
What should we do?
They look pretty serious.
- Just go ahead and try!
- Head Teacher!
Go on! He'll run away!
- Yeah, but...
- Never mind and do it!
- Look out, sir!
- They'll kill you! Run!
I will never forgive those who
would try to destroy this school!
Being a teacher is the only
thing for me.
My family opened my
eyes to that.
That's why I will protect
this school!
Some time has passed since.
As of yet, both sides are
at an impasse.
Students and parents have
gathered around the school
and are cheering
on the teachers.
Aizawa-san, do you have
any comments?
Can we have a word from you?
Just what is going to happen
with this situation?
What are they doing, letting that
trash get away with this?
Tôdô-san!
What's going on here!
Hurry and remove those people!
Yes, but...
This is no longer Seirin
Academy!
They have no business
being here.
I understand.
Go ahead!
I'll take responsibility, go ahead!
Okay.
- Hurry!
- Kotani-sensei!
You have to protect
Onizuka-sensei!
What are you doing? Hurry!
Yes!
Nakamaru-sensei,
are you alright?
Hey! What ya think you're doing
to my student?!
Hey, you've been hired by us.
You think we'll let this go?
You think I'd ever go
to your school?
- Please listen!
- What is it, Head Teacher?
We've worked so hard
and thought we were creating
a rich Japan, a rich world.
But we were mistaken!
This Japan now, has no wealth!
- It's a heartlessly poor world!
- Dear...
- So you see, I cannot bear it!
- You're awesome, Papa...
Even if you could say I created it,
these bad laws, bad leadership...
We have to tear it down!
22ND ANNUAL MUSASHINO
SEIRIN ACADEMY'S
CAMPUS FESTIVAL!
Welcome to Seirin Academy's
school festival!
Everyone, come on in!
Welcome!
Director!
I'd forgotten!
Today's the school festival!
- Mike test! Testing!
- Sensei!
Alright! Come on in!
Come on in!
We've got takoyaki, a haunted
house, fortune telling, everything!
And for all you cuties,
a Ms. Loose Socks contest!
And featuring our Academy Idol,
Nomura Tomoko on stage!
Of course we've got a fan
goods shop!
Better hurry, it sells out fast!
Hey, make sure you get it right!
So this is what you
wanted to do?
Yeah, well...
See, I never went to a school
festival when I was a kid.
So you see...
This is my first school festival.
So, you were working
to raise funds?
Oh, geeze!
Alright!
Shall we kick it off!
Miyabi, forgive me.
Mama's going to quit
appearing on TV.
Why?
Because.
This is great!
Okay!
FROM: TOKYO DISTRICT PUBLIC
PROSECUTORS OFFICE
TO: TÔDÔ SHIN'ICHI
What a bother!
Yes, I'm at a loss!
Yohoo!
You don't understand
a thing, do you?
Raising this ruckus is useless!
You don't get it, do you?
All of this is ours!
Whatever we want, to destroy it
or whatever, it's our right!
Man, what grumpy old farts!
Why don't you do what
you want?
How 'bout I give you a hand?
What's that?!
Even if there's no buildings.
Musashino Seirin Academy
will not disappear.
What do you mean?
Whether it be under the open
skies or any other conditions,
we can have classes anywhere,
as long as there are teachers
and students.
That's called education, isn't it?
Got it?
You! What are you doing!
Go find someone else.
I can't tear this place down.
We're from the Tokyo
Prosecutors Office.
Tôdô-san,
we received this from your son.
We have some questions
for the two of you.
There's an investigation,
about last time's assault, and this
occupation of this building.
Don't worry, he'll be right back.
Onizuka-sensei.
That's the first time.
The first time you've addressed
me like that, Head Teacher.
Onizuka-sensei.
This...
This is the first time,
I've had such an enjoyable
school festival.
Onitchi!
Onizuka! Hang in there!
Alright!
Let's continue the school festival!
With that incident behind us,
the students will be happily
entering their third year.
We can look forward to next
year's class.
We'll be counting on all of you,
I'd like you to work hard
to insure university
admittance rates.
Our Academy's students
are all talented.
I believe they will be admitted
to good universities.
Because you see, this academy
has no trash.
I'll be counting on you, Principal.
Yes!
Director!
What did you just say?
Yes, I'll be counting on you,
Principal Uchiyamada.
And so, the head teacher's
position
will go to Nakamaru-sensei.
I'm truly honored,
but I have to decline.
What? Why?
I feel there is someone much
more suitable for the position.
M-Me?!
Uh, no, that wouldn't be good!
Um, would you all please
reconsider?
Really...
- No apologies now!
- I'm sorry!
Thank you for your patience,
the aircraft will soon
be departing.
Let's tighten up your belt, okay?
- There!
- Thank you!
So he hasn't called at all
since then?
Your knight in shining armor?
Just where'd he disappear to?
Now then, let's get to work!
Hello, this is L4, Fuyutsuki?
Yes?
Will you do something
about that?
He's saying he won't move
until you get off.
Well then, I'll be counting on you,
Onizuka-kun.
Leave it to me, Director!
Alright then!
FUYUTSUKI AZUSA
So, I'm gonna be your homeroom
teacher from today,
name's Fuyutsuki Azusa,
anyone gotta problem with that?
- Sensei, it doesn't suit you.
- I guess so!
Alright then everyone,
let's give it our best today!
Humans should cherish
life more, don't you think?
There's no such thing
as a rehearsal for life.
- Stop this recklessness!
- Sensei!
Stop it!
Sensei, what should I do?
Do whatever you want!
You should be you!
Love isn't about status!
Do you realize what you
are doing, Onizuka?
You'll be fired! If you do this,
you'll be fired immediately!
How's this? Feels great,
doesn't it?
You are all great!
Hey Miyabi, where are you?
Princess, have you been injured?
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Were you really referred
by Director Sakurai?
Of course!
Oh, didn't you two
see me on TV?
Um, are you certain there isn't
any mistakes here?
- There's just one thing...
- What is it?
My first great personal
experience...
There's no need to go into that.
Really? Bummers.
Although to me it was my
greatest achievement of my life.
Onizuka-sensei, why have you
come to this school?
What? Well, you see...
Because I want to be a teacher!
2016-09